

GABRIEL CHIPAYA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CAREER OVERVIEW

I am a software developer with experience in mobile/web application design, and development. I am skilled in React, React Native, and Next.js. React is a JavaScript library used for building user interfaces (UIs) for web and mobile applications. React Native is a framework for building mobile applications using JavaScript and React. Next.js is a full-stack React framework for building serverside rendered (SSR) React applications.

KEY COMPETENCIES

- HTML, CSS, Tailwind
- React, React Native, NextIs
- Nodels, Expressls
- Mongodb, MySql
- UX/UI Design
- Application Development
- Project Management
- End to End Testing
- Process Optimization

CONTACT ME AT:

Email: gabechipaya@gmail.com

Phone: +260 979 788911

github: https://github.com/GABE400?

tab=repositories

Address: Lusaka, Zambia

Website: https://www.gabrielthedeveloper.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Voluntary Work as a Live Streamer

Revival Fire Missions | July 2020 - present

- Online Streaming using V-Mix or Prism Live Studio
- Working with graphic designs using photoshop

Freelance

Full-stack Developer | Jan 2022 - present

- Responsibility includes developing react projects
- Using Vite, React Native, Nextjs 13, Tailwind CSS, Prisma, tRPC, NextAuth.js, TypeScript, Express.js and Node.js

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH



Bachelor of Science (Hons) in computing | Aug 2020 - Dec 2021

- BSc with Honours in Computing
- Took advanced courses on Human-Computer Interaction Design, Requirements Management and mobile application design, and development
- Participated in enterprise system projects

ZCAS UNIVERSITY | NCC Education

NCC Diploma in computing | Feb 2016 - Dec 2019

- Advanced Diploma in Computing
- Specialized in software development
- NCC Awarding Great Britis
- Database Design and Development
- Agile Development
- Software Development Techniques
- Computer Systems



WORK REFERENCES

Abel Zulu

Head of the media team, Revival Fire Missions

Phone: +260 97 7439535